

PERSONAL BACKGROUND

Experienced digital marketing specialist with demonstrated history of working in the digital marketing divisions in several industries. I have long track record of creating and implementing successful social media campaigns. Over the years I gained experience in market analysis, creating reports for social media and tracking KPI's on daily and monthly basis, managing CRM systems and budget managing for social media activities.

SKILLS AND EXPERTISE

- Social Media Strategy
- Digital Marketing
- Market Research
- Photography and Photoshop
- Photo Editing
- Canva
- Content writing
- Facebook and Instagram Ads

GET IN TOUCH WITH ME

Phone: (+389) 70378091

Address: Shekspirova 1/2 - 10, 1000 Skopje, North

Macedonia

Email: blazheska.zorica@gmail.com LinkedIn: zorica-blazeska

ZORICA BLAZESKA

Digital Marketing Specialist

WORK EXPERIENCE

Marketing and Communication Associate

Sparkasse Bank AD Skopje | Dec 2021 - on going

- Coordination with marketing and digital agencies
- Creating and implementing digital marketing strategy for Sparkasse Bank AD Skopje
- Creating yearly marketing plan including product, PR, digital, CSR projects
- Creating marketing solutions for paid marketing campaigns
- Implementing digital campaigns (Facebook, Instagram, GDN)
- Creating reports for digital channels (Facebook, Instagram, GDN) and keeping track of KPIs on daily and monthly basis
- Developing content for social media
- Budget managing for digital activities
- Creating strategy and analyst ATL and BTL campaigns
- Managing POS materials
- Organizing events and CSR projects
- Managing with PR strategy and writing PR articles
- Writing and managing internal newsletter

Digital Marketing Specialist

Philip Morris International | May 2021 - Nov 2021

- Coordination with local and regional marketing agency
- Implementing digital marketing strategy for IQOS
- Creating marketing solutions for paid marketing campaigns
- Implementing campaigns on social media (Facebook and Instagram)
- Publishing posts on social media and using Sprinklr and Facebook Creator studio
- Creating reports on social media and keeping track of KPIs on daily and monthly basis $\,$
- Market analysis
- Developing content for social media
- Implementing viber campaings with Sprinklr and email marketing campaigns
- Performance analysis
- Managing CRM
- Budget managing for Social media activities
- Budget planning

Digital Marketing Specialist

Vrabotuvanje.com | Feb 2021 - May 2021

- managing social media profiles (Facebook, Instagram, Linkedin)
- creating Facebook ads\ Instagram ads
- developing creatives for posts on social media
- Researching competitors and using SEO for keywords on website
- monitoring, track, analyse and report on performance on social media platforms using tools such as Google Analytics and Facebook insights
- writing articles on daily basis for the website \ copywriting
- Interviews
- writing PR text's
- creating and implementing marketing strategies for clients
- Employer branding companies
- Customer care support

COURSES

JOUNALISM Youth Educational Forum \ 2015 Introductory training for young journalists introduction to communication | work ethics| interview| photography| column | reportag

Skills for Success - MOTIVA education center of PIVARA Skopje 2021

GOOGLE ADS Masterclass by LeanSEM

Content Writer | Social Media Manager

eXpressive graphics | feb 2021 -

Creating content for Social Media chanells for:

- Grand Burger
- Jägermeister
- Zid na zdravjeto
- naracaj.mk

Marketing Assistant

Tehnokomerc AD | Oct 2020 - Dec 2020

- managing e-commerce shop
- Creating content for social media channels
- Implementing marketing and advertising campaigns
- Managing pages on social media (Facebook, Instagram)
- Customer care support

Marketing Coordinator - Internship

Creative hub | Jul 2020 - Oct 2020

- Implementing marketing and advertising campaigns
- Preparing marketing and advertising strategies
- Creating and managing Facebook Ads\ LinkedIn ads
- Planning and organizing promotional presentations
- Cold Calling
- Creating email marketing campaigns and using MailChimp and Hubspot
- Creating content and copywriting
- Managing pages on social media (Facebook, LinkedIn, Instagram)

LANGUAGES:

- Macedonian
- English
- Spanish

LEAD GENERATION SPECIALIST

Freelancing | Jun 2020 - ongoing

- -Updating Exciting
- Contact Database
- Creating Database
- Data Mining
- Email List Building
- Lead Generation
- Data Entry
- Email Expert

DIGITAL MARKETING INTERN

Axeltra | Nov 2019 - Feb 2020

- -Performing market research activities
- Helping in pre-sales activities (lead generation and lead qualification).
- Assisting in internet marketing activities
- Being part of creating email marketing campaings

SALES MARKETING ASSISTANT

Urban Invest | Oct 2018 - Nov 2018

- Research of the market
- Creating databases
- Creating email marketing campaings and using MailChimp
- Presenting product and sales

INTERN

NLB Bank | Jun 2017 - Jul 2017

-I was intern in the department of payment operations and pay office, including promotive campaigns for - Mastercard credit cards and NLBclick mobile banking

I was intern in the department for payment operations, debit and credit cards. I was also promoter for the promoting activity: "Ден на пензионерите - повеќе за вашето здравје"

EDUCATION

Creative Hub

Digital Marketing and Account Management Academy

- CONTENT (Copywriting, Adobe Photoshop, PR)
- MEDIA (Facebook Ads Manager Professional, LinkedIn Advertising Professional, Email Marketing and CRM, Relationship Based Lead Generation and Sales, Google Ads, You Tube Ads, SEO+Wordpress+HTML5, Google Analytics, Landing Pages
- COMMUNICATION (Account Management)

University of Ss Cyril and Methodius - Faculty of Economics

Bachelor of Marketing in Economics, 2015 - on hold

University of Ss. Cyril and Methodius - Faculty of Law Iustinianus Primus

Bachelor of Public Relations, 2021- ongoing